JASMINE QUACH-CAIN

Former fashion design student turned Accountant, and finally returning to school for Software Development after craving more of a creative and fulfilling career. I view Software as another creative outlet that is challenging, yet fun and addictive.

From a young age, my curiosity got the best of me, which lead me to coding Xanga/Myspace layouts as a hobby and feeding my creative side.

Additionally, my background and experience ranges from small business, accounting, and management, to repairing iPhones and related hardware, graphic design, and some WordPress.



XJASMINEQUACH@GMAIL.COM



615.603.6650



JASMINEQUACH.COM



GITHUB.COM/JASMINEQ



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/JASMINEQUACH

EDUCATION

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL

Full Stack Software Engineer

O'MORE COLLEGE OF DESIGN Fashion Designer

WORK EXPERIENCE

DEC 2018 TO PRESENT LOTUS APPS CONTRACT SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

· Customer Service App: Rails Testing with Capybara, Rspec and Factorybot

2018 TO PRESENT FREELANCE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Hybrid Mobile App in Ionic 3/Angular 5; CORS configuration for Rails API
- Event App: Implementing new front-end designs and Rails API resources on WebApp and Ionic 3/ Angular 4 Mobile App
- Local Transportation Company: Customized WP theme runs on Pantheon
- LifeIsOrganized: Supported Custom Built WP theme, converted MailChimp integration to CovertKit
- Optometrist Marketing Site: Customized WP theme, Photoshop cropping

PROJECTS

FABRIC IPSUM

- Fabric Ipsum is a SPA that generates Ipsum paragraphs based on words from a fabric dictionary built in Ruby On Rails.
- https://fabric-ipsum.herokuapp.com/

2017

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL APPRENTICE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Immersive 6-month coding boot camp emphasizing front-end, backend technologies, group projects and Agile/SCRUM methodology.
- Created SPAs using Git, Javascript, jQuery, Angular JS, Grunt, HTML5, SCSS, JSON, and AJAX
- Worked in groups, exercising best practices in workflow via Trello and Github Projects
- Practiced workflow in a simulated team-oriented work environment, including daily stand-ups with technical manager and product owner
- Created RESTful API's with Ruby on Rails
- Retrieved and store database information in Firebase, and SQLite
- Unit testing and TDD with Minitest

PROJECTS

BOBBIN

 A project management app for sewing, embroidery and craft enthusiasts. Built with AngularJS, UI router, and nested components. App prompts user to login via OAuth 2 Authentication bobbin-ang.firebaseapp.com

FABRIC MUCH

- Fabric Much is an inventory tracking app for craft supplies to avoid duplicates or shortages on items. Front-end: Built-in AngularJS, UI router with nested components. Back-end: Rails API, JWT Auth, and a join table.
- fabric-much.firebaseapp.com/

2016 - 2017 KROGER CORPORATE ACCOUNTS PAYABLE LEAD

- Oversee Alcohol accounts/reports using Fintech
- Responsible for Direct Store Delivery Vendors for four districts
- Balancing District accounts
- Analyze and verify data before approving claims